Guide to the Kate Millett papers, 1912-2002, bulk 1951-2001 RL.10070
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Farm Papers, 1974-1999; 6 boxes
  - Administrative Files, 1976-1999 and undated
    - 1985, Farm volunteers note (Box F4)
    - 1988-1991 and undated, Eastern Spruce Gall Adelgid and insecticide information
      - "Spruce Gall Adelgid: All we know so far," file names Adelgid and Adelgid.bk!, 1990 Sept. 21 (Disk018) (Box F4)
    - 1989, Farm invitation form letter (Box F4)
    - 1989 and undated, Literature on the Farm (Box F4)
    - 1989, Volunteer harvesters, correspondence, 2 folders (Box F4)
    - 1989-1991, Electronic format only: Resident contact information
      - 1989 summer contact sheet, file name Summer, 1989 Aug. 30 (Disk017) (Box F4)
      - Address for Abbott Sydney, file name Obon, 1991 July 19 (Disk017) (Box F4)
      - Some numbers [for a merge file?], file name Obonmerg, 1990 July 12 (Disk017) (Box F4)
    - 1989-1991 and undated, Farm tenant correspondence (Box F4)
    - 1989-1991,1998 and undated, Advertising and publicity (Box F4)
    - 1989-1991 and undated, Tax information and budget notes (Box F4)
    - 1990, Contact between Lenox lumber and Leslie Pederson (Box F4)
    - 1990, Farm invitation form letters (Box F4)
    - 1990, Farm reunion invitation (Box F5)
    - 1990, Farm tenant lease agreements (Box F5)
    - 1990, Harvest festival invitation (Box F5)
    - 1990, Electronic format only: Letter to publishers requesting donations for the farm
      - Letter to publishers, file name Pubmerg, 1990 July 12 (Disk017) (Box F5)
      - Address for Basic Books, file name Publish, 1990 July 12 (Disk017) (Box F5)
      - List of numbers (for merge file?), file name Pubenv, 1990 July 12 (Disk017) (Box F5)
    - 1990-1991, Electronic format only: Form letters
      - Invitation to farm reunion, file name Reunion, 1990 Mar. 1 (Disk017) (Box F5)
      - Letter on occupying the farm in the fall, file names Farmfall and Farmfall.bk!, 1990 Oct. 6 (Disk019) (Box F5)
      - Harvest festival invitation, file name Harvest, 1990 Dec. 2 (Disk019) (Box F5)
      - Farm invitation letter, file name Farmlett, 1991 Feb. 23 (Disk019) (Box F5)
      - Farm invitation letter (shortened), file name Farmshrt, 1991 Feb. 23 (Disk019) (Box F5)
      - To friends of the farm, file name Planting, 1991 Mar. 28 (Disk017) (Box F5)
      - Invitation for farm open house, file name Farm-nei, 1991 July 25 (Disk019) (Box F5)
    - 1990-1991, Farm advertisement correspondence (Box F5)
    - 1990-1991, Farm planning notes (Box F5)
    - 1990-1991, Harvest receipts and figures (Box F5)
    - 1990-1991, Research requests re: the Farm (Box F5)
    - 1990-1992, Advertising - Lesbian Connection newsletter (Box F5)
    - 1990-1992, Farm advertisements (Box F5)
    - 1990-1992 and undated, Funding search and notes (Box F5)
    - 1990-1992 and undated, Tree order notes and publicity (Box F5)
    - 1990-1992 and undated, Wholesale Christmas tree sales (Box F5)
    - 1991 Aug., Farm newsletter (Box F5)
    - 1991, Christmas tree growers association buyers list (Box F5)
    - 1991-1992 and undated, Christmas tree publicity (Box F5)
    - 1991-1992, Farm invitation form letter (Box F5)
    - 1991-1992 Fall, Resident mailing list (Box F5)
    - 1991-1993 and undated, Farm tenants correspondence (Box F5)
    - 1991-1994 and undated, Forest management certificates and information (Box F5)
    - 1991-1994 and 1997, Linda Kavars funding project for the Farm (Box F5)
    - 1992 Apr. 25, New York Foundation for the Arts (Box F5)
    - 1992 Dec. 3, Article on the Farm (Box F5)
    - 1992, Benefit - general support (Box F5)
    - 1992, Christmas tree advertisements (Box F5)
    - 1992, Christmas tree flyers (Box F5)
    - 1992, Farm business certificate (Box F5)
    - 1992, Fundraising letter (Box F5)
    - 1992, Sleight Farmsubdivisions (Box F5)
    - 1992 and undated, Wholesale Christmas tree sales, 2 folders (Box F5)
    - 1992-1993, Christmas tree industry publications (Box F5)
    - 1992-1994 and undated, Farm budget notes and correspondence (Box F5)
    - 1993, Account of Farm crisis (partial typescript) (Box F5)
    - 1993, Disgruntled Farm participant (Box F5)
    - 1993, Planting invitation form letter (Box F5)
    - 1994 and undated, Master class student writing samples, 2 folders (Box F5)
    - 1994-1995 and undated, Farm tenants correspondence (Box F5)
    - 1995, Millett Farm newsletter (Box F5)
    - 1995 and undated, Visitor schedule (Box F5)
    - 1996, Farm sale (Box F5)
    - 1997, Harvest advertisements and correspondence (Box F6)
    - 1997 and undated, Farm tenants correspondence (Box F6)
    - 1997, Insurance correspondence (Box F6)
    - 1997-1998 and undated, Planting invitation and horticulture information (Box F6)
    - 1998 and undated, Alliance of Artists' Communities (Box F6)
    - 1998, Farm restoration master plan notes (Box F6)
    - 1998, Farm twentieth anniversary invitation (Box F6)
    - 1998, Girlfriends advertisement letter (Box F6)
    - 1998, Nurseryman advertising (Box F6)
    - 1999, Carp stocking permit and correspondence (Box F6)
    - 1999, Forum 99 invitation (Box F6)
    - 1999, Master class correspondence and student writing samples (Box F6)
    - Undated, 501 C3 nonprofit information and blank tax forms (Box F6)
    - Undated, Budget notes (Box F6)
    - Undated, Farm invitation form letters (Box F6)
    - Undated, Farm layout sketch (Box F6)
    - Undated, Kiln instructions (Box F6)
    - Undated, Landscape trees advertisement (Box F6)
    - Undated, New farm invitation form letter (Box F6)
    - Undated, Note on field signs (Box F6)
    - Undated, Notes and to-do lists (Box F6)
    - Undated, Notes on Linda Kavars (Box F6)
    - Undated, Party invitation (Box F6)
    - Undated, Quotations from residents on farm experience (Box F6)
    - Undated, Research paper on the Farm - Linda Clarke (Box F6)
    - Undated Review of Danielle Willis play (Box F6)
    - Undated, Visitor schedule (Box F6)
- Course Materials, 1951-1999; 13 boxes
  The bulk of this series consists of reading notes and lecture notes from Millett's work as a student and as a professor. The series also contains Millett's student papers, papers written by her own students, and correspondence and other material related to her university activities. Millett's undergraduate work at the University of Minnesota and Oxford University is well represented, and some material is available from Millett's graduate work at Columbia University. Teaching materials are primarily from Millett's work at Barnard College and California State University at Sacramento.
  The series is divided into two subseries for Millett's student work and teaching materials, and is in chronological order within each subseries. However, it is sometimes unclear whether notes from the 1960s represent student or teaching work, since Millett both taught and completed her graduate work during this period.
  - Student Work, 1951-circa 1968
    - 1951, 1955 and undated, Notes and bibliography, 18th Century (Box CM1)
    - 1952-1968 and undated, Course materials, school pamphlets, and writings (Box CM1)
    - 1953, English History notes and exams (Box CM1)
    - 1953, Milton, notes and exam (Box CM1)
    - 1953 and undated, Music books and notes (Box CM1)
    - 1954, English History, notes and exams (Box CM1)
    - Circa 1954, Modern World History, syllabus and notes, 2 folders (Box CM1)
    - Circa 1954, "My Own Sophomore Survey at Minnesota," notes (Box CM1)
    - 1955 Spring, Modern World History, notes and syllabus (Box CM1)
    - 1955 Fall, Notes and papers, 18th Century (Box CM1)
    - 1955, European History notes and exams (Box CM2)
    - 1955, Modern Drama, notes (Box CM2)
    - 1955 and undated, Poetry, notes and papers (Box CM2)
    - 1955, Shakespeare notes (Box CM2)
    - 1955, Theatre notes (Box CM2)
    - 1955-1956, 18th Century, notes, papers, and exams, 2 folders (Box CM2)
    - 1956 Winter, 18th Century notes and papers (Box CM2)
    - 1956 Winter, Bible, notes and syllabus (Box CM2)
    - 1956 Winter, Chaucer, notes and exams (Box CM2)
    - 1956 Winter, Poetry, notes and papers (Box CM3)
    - 1956, Senior Prose Seminar, notes and papers (Box CM3)
    - 1956, Art 50, notes and papers (Box CM3)
    - 1956, Art notes, papers, and handouts, University of Minnesota (Box CM3)
    - 1956, B.A. diploma, University of Minnesota (Box CM3)
    - 1956, "Conduct and Discipline of Junior Members of the University," pamphlet, Oxford (Box CM3)
    - 1956 and undated, Oxford, "The 15th and 16th Century", 2 folders (Box CM3)
    - Circa 1956, University of Minnesota transcript (Box CM3)
    - 1957, Hilary Term, Oxford, "17th C. Papers and notes", 2 folders (Box CM3)
    - 1957-1958 and undated, Oxford, correspondence and notes on Dobson (Box CM3)
    - Circa 1958, Oxford, "18th C." notes (Box CM3)
    - Circa 1958, Oxford, "18th C., Pope's couplet," notes and essay (Box CM3)
    - Circa 1958, Oxford, "18th C. and misc./Swift," notes (Box CM4)
    - Circa 1958, Oxford "18th C., Swift, his masks," notes and essay (Box CM4)
    - 1958, Oxford, Chaucer and contemporaries, notes (Box CM4)
    - 1958, Oxford, Modern English (Box CM4)
    - 1958, Hilary Term, Oxford, Old English notes and paper, 2 folders (Box CM4)
    - 1950s, Abnormal Psychology notes, University of Minnesota (Box CM4)
    - 1950s, British literature, Eng. 22, University of Minnesota (Box CM4)
    - 1950s, British literature, Eng. 23, University of Minnesota (Box CM4)
    - 1950s, Chaucer vocabulary notebook, University of Minnesota (Box CM4)
    - 1950s, English History notes, University of Minnesota (Box CM4)
    - 1950s, English literature notes, University of Minnesota (Box CM4)
    - 1950s, French literature notes, University of Minnesota, 1-2 of 3 folders (Box CM4)
    - 1950s, French literature notes, University of Minnesota, 3 of 3 folders (Box CM5)
    - 1950s, Humanities notes and exams, University of Minnesota, 2 folders (Box CM5)
    - 1950s, Janey Washburn, notes and exams, University of Minnesota (Box CM5)
    - 1950s, Literature of the Bible, notes, University of Minnesota, 2 folders (Box CM5)
    - 1950s, Music notes, University of Minnesota (Box CM5)
    - 1950s, Myth in Literature, notes and papers, University of Minnesota (Box CM5)
    - 1950s, Mythology notes, University of Minnesota (Box CM5)
    - 1950s, Notes and typescript, "New Orleans Jazz," University of Minnesota (Box CM5)
    - 1950s, Psychology notes, University of Minnesota, 2 folders (Box CM5)
    - 1950s, Shakespeare, Eng 21, University of Minnesota (Box CM5)
    - 1950s, Oxford, "The 18th C." notes (Box CM5)
    - 1950s, Oxford, "19th C. Victorian English," essay and notes (Box CM5)
    - 1950s, Oxford, "American English" notes (Box CM5)
    - 1950s, Oxford, "Foreign Influences of English" notes (Box CM5)
    - 1950s, Oxford, Milton and Spencer notes, 2 folders (Box CM5)
    - 1950s, Oxford, "Modern English" notes (Box CM5)
    - 1950s, Oxford, "Norman Conquest" notes (Box CM5)
    - 1950s and undated, Oxford, The Novel, notes (Box CM6)
    - 1950s, Oxford, "Renaissance and Great Vowel Shift" notes (Box CM6)
    - 1950s, Oxford, "Romantics," notes and essays, 2 folders (Box CM6)
    - 1950s, Oxford, Shakespearean drama, notes and papers, 2 folders (Box CM6)
    - 1950s, "Tutorial lecture" notes (Box CM6)
    - 1950s, Beowulf notes and essay, 2 folders (Box CM6)
    - 1950s, Notes on Keats, Shelley, Byron, Hazlitt (Box CM6)
    - 1950s, Shakespearean drama notes, 2 folders (Box CM6)
    - 1963, French exam (Box CM6)
    - 1963-1964, Graduate school admission (Box CM6)
    - 1964 and undated, Sir Gawain and the Green Knight translation (Box CM7)
    - 1966, Chaucer notes (Box CM7)
    - 1966, Columbia, German notes and exam (Box CM7)
    - 1966, Doctoral seminar paper, "Walter Pater and the Art of Sculpture," first draft (Box CM7)
    - 1966, Doctoral seminar paper, "Walter Pater and the Art of Sculpture," second draft (Box CM7)
    - Circa 1966, "Pater Paper, 1st Draft" (Box CM7)
    - Circa 1968, Women and literature note cards (Box CM7)
    - 1960s, Columbia, Carlyle reading notes (Box CM7)
    - 1960s, Columbia – Chaucer notes (Box CM7)
    - 1960s, Essay drafts on women in literature (Box CM7)
    - 1960s, Jean Genet notes (Box CM7)
    - 1960s, Latin and French notes and exercises (Box CM7)
    - Circa 1960s, Note cards and notes on female sexuality, 2 folders (Box CM7)
    - 1960s, Reading notes on Pater, 2 folders (Box CM7)
    - Undated, Bacon notes (Box CM7)
    - Undated, Bibliography in English literature, note cards, 1 of 4 folders (Box CM7)
    - Undated, Bibliography in English literature, note cards, 2-4 of 4 folders (Box CM8)
    - Undated, Canterbury Tales notes, 2 folders (Box CM8)
    - Undated, History of English, Indo–European/Germanic notes (Box CM8)
    - Undated, History of English, linguistics notes (Box CM8)
    - Undated, History of English, Middle English notes (Box CM8)
    - Undated, History of English, Old English notes (Box CM8)
    - Undated, History of English, phonetics notes (Box CM8)
    - Undated, Latin notes and exercises (Box CM8)
    - Undated, Middle English notes (Box CM8)
    - Undated, Minor Poems notes (Box CM8)
    - Undated, Troilus and Cressida notes (Box CM8)
  - Teaching Material, circa 1959-1999 and undated
    - Circa 1959, Notes and lectures, Freshman English, University of North Carolina at Greensboro (Box CM8)
    - 1958-1960s, Othello and tragedy notes, Oxford and Barnard (Box CM8)
    - Circa 1962, Lectures on English Literature, Waseda (Box CM8)
    - 1963, Notebook, "Hunter - freshman" (Box CM9)
    - 1964 Fall, English A1, Barnard (Box CM9)
    - 1964, Administrative materials, Hunter College (Box CM9)
    - 1964 and undated, Lecture notes and Manhattan Community College course information (Box CM9)
    - 1964-1968 and undated, University contracts and correspondence (Box CM9)
    - 1965, Freshman English (Box CM9)
    - 1965-1968 and undated, English 93, notes, handouts, and student work (Box CM9)
    - 1966 and undated, Barnard correspondence (Box CM9)
    - 1966-1967 and undated, "Books to Order", 3 folders (Box CM9)
    - 1966-circa 1968 and undated, Student correspondence (Box CM9)
    - 1966-1995, Student records (Box CM9)
    - 1967 Jan., English 93 final exams (Box CM9)
    - 1967 May, Barnard newsletter and announcements (Box CM9)
    - 1967 and undated, Book catalogs (Box CM9)
    - 1967, Recommendation (Box CM9)
    - 1967-1968 and undated, Barnard newsletter and book catalogs, 1 of 2 folders (Box CM9)
    - 1967-1968 and undated, Barnard newsletter and book catalogs, 2 of 2 folders (Box CM10)
    - 1967-1968 and undated, Grade books, Barnard, 2 folders (Box CM10)
    - 1967-1969 and undated, Notes, student work, and exam (Box CM10)
    - 1968 June, Student paper, Barnard (Box CM10)
    - 1968 and undated, The Avant-Garde, Barnard, handouts and notes (Box CM10)
    - 1968 and undated, English A, Barnard, class list and notes (Box CM10)
    - 1968-1969 and undated, Materials for student recommendations (Box CM10)
    - 1969 and undated, Cinema, notes and student papers, 3 folders (Box CM10)
    - 1960s, The Avant-Garde, Barnard, handouts and notes (Box CM10)
    - 1960s, "Beckett 'Novels,'" notes (Box CM10)
    - 1960s, "Beckett's Plays," notes (Box CM10)
    - 1960s, Dante notes, Barnard (Box CM10)
    - 1960s, English 4, Barnard, notes and handouts (Box CM10)
    - 1960s, English 4, notes and syllabus (Box CM10)
    - 1960s, English 93, Barnard, notes on comedy (Box CM10)
    - 1960s, English 93 conference sign–up sheet (Box CM10)
    - 1960s, English A, Barnard (Box CM10)
    - 1960s, Exams in English Literature, [Waseda?] (Box CM10)
    - 1960s, Flannery O'Connor notes (Box CM10)
    - 1960s, Grade book and student paper, Barnard (Box CM11)
    - 1960s, Hamlet notes (Box CM11)
    - 1960s, Happenings notes (Box CM11)
    - 1960s, Herman Hesse notes (Box CM11)
    - 1960s, Kafka notes (Box CM11)
    - 1960s, King Lear notes and quiz (Box CM11)
    - 1960s, Lolita notes (Box CM11)
    - 1960s, Marat/ Sade notes (Box CM11)
    - Circa 1960s, Notes (Box CM11)
    - 1960s, Oliver Twist notes (Box CM11)
    - 1960s, Richard III notes (Box CM11)
    - 1960s, "Survey I" notes (Box CM11)
    - 1960s, "Survey II" notes (Box CM11)
    - 1960s, Thomas Mann notes (Box CM11)
    - 1960s, "The Very Contemporary Arts" course proposal, Barnard (Box CM11)
    - 1960s, William S. Burroughs notes (Box CM11)
    - 1970-1971 and undated, Bryn Mawr correspondence and Sociology of Women course materials (Box CM11)
    - Circa 1973, Bibliographies (Box CM11)
    - 1973 and undated, Essays and request for recommendation, Barbara Pollack (Box CM11)
    - 1973, Prisons and Prison Movement notes and course materials (Box CM11)
    - 1973, Prisons class, student papers, 1-4 of 5 folders (Box CM11)
    - 1973, Prisons class, student papers, 5 of 5 folders (Box CM12)
    - 1973, Sacramento State University, grading (Box CM12)
    - 1973, Student paper, "The Golden Notebook" (Box CM12)
    - 1973 and undated, University of California at Berkeley correspondence and information (Box CM12)
    - 1973 and undated, Woman Writers course materials and Sacramento feminist announcements and correspondence (Box CM12)
    - 1973, Women Writers, student papers, 3 folders (Box CM12)
    - 1974 and undated, Correspondence and course planning, University of California at Berkeley (Box CM12)
    - 1975, Student writing journals (Box CM12)
    - 1979-1984, 1992 and undated, Letters of recommendation and supporting material, 2 folders (Box CM12)
    - 1990-1991, Electronic format only: Letters of recommendation
      - Recommendation for Jenny Cox, file name Jennylet, 1990 Mar. 18 (Disk019) (Box CM12)
      - Recommendation for Jennifer Floryan for a film internship, file name Jenlet1, 1990 Nov. 17 (Disk019) (Box CM12)
      - Incomplete recommendation for Jennifer Floryan, file name Jen-rec, 1990 Nov. 28 (Disk019) (Box CM12)
      - Paragraph on Jennifer Floryan for recommendation, file name Jen-chi, 1990 Dec. 29 (Disk019) (Box CM12)
      - Recommendation for Jennifer Floryan [for chiropractic school], file name Jen-chir, 1990 Dec. 29 (Disk019) (Box CM12)
      - Recommendation for Maureen Riley, file name Recriley, 1991 Jan. 1 (Disk017) (Box CM12)
      - Recommendation for Jennifer Floryan, file name Jennyu, 1991 Mar. 13 (Disk019) (Box CM12)
    - 1997, New York University correspondence and bulletins, 1-2 of 3 folders (Box CM12)
    - 1997, New York University correspondence and bulletins, 3 of 3 folders (Box CM13)
    - 1999 Spring, New York University, Feminism and the Novel, lecture notes and class lists (Box CM13)
    - 1999 Spring, New York University class administration and student evaluations (Box CM13)
    - Undated, English 3 syllabus, assignment, and lecture notes (Box CM13)
    - Undated, Ionesco notes (Box CM13)
    - Undated, Lectures on poetry (Box CM13)
    - Undated, Modern French Theatre notes (Box CM13)
    - Undated, "Prose Style and Essays (Miles)" notes (Box CM13)
    - Undated, Southern Rhetoric and Heart of Darkness lecture notes (Box CM13)
    - Undated, "Tindall's Lectures" notes (Box CM13)
- Personal Files, 1949-2002; 6 boxes
  Arranged in the following subseries: Financial Papers, Medical Papers, Legal Papers, Helen Millett, Loft Papers, and Other Personal Files. The last contains address books, job search records, and other personal records. The bulk of the series consists of financial records, records of Helen Millett's final years, and documentation of Millett's involvement in the Cooper Square Committee and her ongoing fight to preserve artists' lofts in that area. Records are arranged chronologically within each subseries.
  Additional personal records can be found throughout the collection. See also the Correspondence, Subject, Writings and Speeches, and Farm Series.
  - Financial Papers, 1958-circa 1996
    - 1958, Bank statement (Box P1)
    - 1958-1959 and undated, Notes and financial papers (Box P1)
    - 1965-1966, Check register and receipts (Box P1)
    - 1967-1973 and undated, Electric bills and Sacramento State University separation papers (Box P1)
    - 1969 and 1974-1976, Bank statements (Box P1)
    - 1973, Bank accounts, various projects (Box P1)
    - 1973-1993, Income, receipts, and bank statements (Box P1)
    - 1974, Income, receipts, and bank statements (Box P1)
    - 1974, Income tax return and correspondence (Box P1)
    - Circa 1979, Sophie's farm contract correspondence and negotiations (Box P1)
    - 1980, German bank statements (Box P1)
    - 1981 and undated, Bank card inquiry (Box P1)
    - 1984, Sophie's loan/Brooklyn Project (Box P1)
    - 1990, Clothes receipt (Box P1)
    - 1991, Social Security earnings statement (Box P1)
    - 1991, Electronic format only: Income for 1990
      - file name Inctax90, 1991 Apr. 5 (Disk019) (Box P1)
    - 1992-1993 and undated, Yellow sofa sale (Box P1)
    - 1993-1994, Tax returns (Box P1)
    - 1995, Receipts, trip to St. Paul (Box P1)
    - 1996, Mortgage (Box P1)
    - 1996 and undated, St. Paul flat – mortgage, renters, sale, 2 folders (Box P1)
    - Undated, Estate planning forms [blank] (Box P1)
  - Legal Papers, 1974-1986
    - 1974 and undated, Psychiatric services billing dispute and legal services billing dispute (Box P1)
    - 1974-1979 and undated, Psychiatric services billing dispute and Millett's refusal to pay (Box P1)
    - 1980-1981 and undated, Debts – Bookmark and Page (Box P1)
    - 1983-1986, Legal correspondence and workshop teaching contract (Box P1)
  - Medical Papers, circa 1964-circa 1993
    - 1964-1979 and undated, Health and life insurance (Box P1)
    - 1974, Interview request on mental health issues (Box P1)
    - 1979, Visit to doctor (Box P1)
    - 1980, Blood tests in St. Paul (Box P1)
    - 1980-1990 and undated, Health and life insurance (Box P1)
    - 1992-1993 and undated, Medication and mental health notes and resources (Box P1)
  - Helen Millett ("Mother Millett"), 1949-1994
    - 1949-1984, Legal and financial records (Box P1)
    - 1954-1967, Retirement policy (Box P1)
    - 1956-1991 and undated, Personal correspondence (Box P2)
    - 1967, "My Trip Around the World", 2 folders (Box P2)
    - 1967, "My Trip Around the World," Helen Millett's correspondence to friends (Box P2)
    - 1990, Nursing home directory (Box P2)
    - 1990-1992 and undated, Health care information, 3 folders (Box P2)
    - 1991 and undated, Kate Millett's visit to St. Paul, 2 folders (Box P2)
    - 1991 and undated, Legal and medical papers (Box P2)
    - 1991 and undated, Minnesota work (Box P2)
    - 1991-1992, Medical records (Box P2)
    - 1991-1993 and undated, "St. Paul allies" (Box P2)
    - 1993, Contract for home care provider (Box P2)
    - 1993, Funeral announcement (Box P2)
    - 1994, Estate (Box P2)
    - 1993, Independence News (Box P2)
  - Loft Papers, 1969-2002
    - 1969, An Alternative Plan for Cooper Square study (Box P3)
    - 1970, Development proposals (map) (Box P3)
    - 1972, Cooper Square Committee, Cooper Square Progress study (Box P3)
    - 1973-1976, Eviction notice and compensation claims (Box P3)
    - 1974 Mar. 22, Urban renewal questionnaire (Box P3)
    - 1974-1982, The New Bowery – rent, insurance, appliances, 3 folders (Box P3)
    - 1974-1983 and undated, "The New Hope" – trying to buy 295 Bowery, 2 folders (Box P3)
    - 1976-1984 and undated, Loft and Cooper Square (Box P3)
    - 1979, New York City artist certification (Box P3)
    - 1979, New York City real estate auction catalog (Box P3)
    - 1979 and undated, Correspondence with city officials and Bowery map (Box P3)
    - 1979-1985, New York Theater Ensemble (Box P3)
    - 1980-1984 and undated, Cooper Square Committee and fight for the loft (Box P3)
    - 1983-1984, Rent fight (Box P3)